Let's start with prop types,
Pervane trleriyle balayalm.
right now we're doing prop type validation in the burger ingredient component.
u anda, Burgert okuma bileenindeki geerli dorulamay yapyoruz.
There we make sure that the type is set so it's required and that it is a string.
Burada, trn gerekli olduundan ve bunun bir dize olduundan emin olun.
I'm not doing any validation in any other component
Baka herhangi bir bileen iin herhangi bir dorulama yapmyorum.
and the reason for this is that here
Ve bunun sebebi ld.
I'm not working on a project which is going to get used by other people,
Bakalar tarafndan kullanlabilecek bir proje zerinde almyorum.
I'm not working on a third party library,
nc taraf ktphanesinde almyorum.
I'm not even working in a developer team.
Bir gelitirici ekibinde almyorum bile.
So a lot of the reasons why properties might be used incorrectly aren't relevant here
Dolaysyla zelliklerin hatal ekilde kullanlmasnn nedenlerinden bir ou burada alakal deildir.
Additionally we'll get logical errors in our application if we forget or assign a wrong key property
Buna ek olarak, yanl anahtar unutursak veya atarsak, uygulamamzda mantksal hatalar
anyways
bulacaz.
and that is why I don't use prop type validation that much in this application.
Ve bu nedenle bu uygulamada bu kadar doru geerlilii kullanmyorum.
Now as an exercise,
imdi egzersiz olarak.
definitely feel free to add prop
Kesinlikle eklemekten ekinmeyin.
type validation to some or all of the components.
Bileenlerin bir ksmna veya tamamna dorulama yazn.
Just keep in mind that you will have to convert them from functional components to class based stateful
ilevsel olarak kullanmak iin iyi bir uygulamadr bileenleri olabildiince ve bu nedenle gerekten mantklysa yapn.
components which isn't bad per se, you can absolutely do that but it's also a good practice to not unnecessarily
Onlar ilevsel bileenlerden snf temelli durum bilgisi olan bileenlere dntrmeniz gerekeceini aklnzda bulundurun; bu kesinlikle
do that and instead use as many stateless functional components as possible and therefore really only
zor olmayan bir ekilde yaplyorsa da ayn zamanda bunu gereksiz yere yapmamak ve bunun yerine pek ok
do it if it makes sense
devlet daha az
but again for practice purposes, feel free to validate more prop types.
Fakat tekrar uygulama iin daha ok pervane trn dorulamaktan ekinmeyin.